February 22nd 2022, an implication about our chief, or I'm right.
Right, we've got to thank you through today.
And I thank you for each person here, God, the time that they spend helping this community.
As such, you keep our city safe, our police safe.
I bring out the two guys, the council members, the mayor,
but the decisions they make that they will be to the benefits of the city,
to the benefit of your kingdom, Father.
Thank you for your son, Jesus Christ.
That's his name, what's right.
Congratulations.
Congratulations to the five of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, another nation, another nation, another nation, another nation.
Invisible for the liberty and justice for all of us.
Four of the Republican-button, let's get the personal appearances.
Five, consent agenda, staff, our commands.
We can provide them six and seven.
Close to a crew.
Take it.
East at five.
Sender.
High.
Dokel.
Davis.
High.
Eight.
Budget amendment.
Number 22-16.
Ms. U.A. Water Dispression.
Mike Addison.
All right, this one's pretty self-explanatory.
It's a reimbursement loan from OWRV.
We have to spend the money first.
We're going to give this money back.
We'll give it back comes in for the normal budget items.
Let me take a motion to approve.
Second.
Parker.
Davis.
High.
Dokel.
East at five.
High.
Thanks, Bob.
Thank you.
Now, in the event of Straton Klein, for Jardier Re-Locancy.
So this is the invoice for Larry Bork,
who's an attorney who's consulting with Jardier Re-Locancy.
Funding for the invoice.
the
second.
Davis.
E-SIMP.
Sunder.
D.
J.